..♪..♪..
Subtitles by FrancisSubs
^.^.^.^.COLORED by.^.^.^.^
® Sud_Arun collections ®
A member of Psagmeno.com
(PANTING)
♪.. Papa was a rollin' stone
My son ..♪
♪.. Wherever he laid his hat
Was his home ..♪
♪.. And when he died ..♪
♪.. All he left us was alone ..♪
♪.. Hey, Papa was a rollin' stone
Dadgummit ..♪
♪.. Wherever he laid his hat
Was his home ..♪
♪.. And when he died ..♪
♪.. All he left us was alone ..♪
♪.. It was the third of September ..♪
♪.. That day I'll always remember
Yes, I will ..♪
♪.. 'Cause that was the day ..♪
♪.. That my daddy died ..♪
♪.. I never got a chance to see him ..♪
♪.. Never heard nothin'
But bad things about him ..♪
♪.. Mama, I'm depending on you ..♪
♪.. To tell me the truth ..♪
♪.. Mama just hung her head
And said, "Son" ..♪
♪.. Papa was a rollin' stone ..♪
(SILENCED GUNSHOT)
(FAINTLY OVER STEREO)
♪.. Wherever he laid his hat ..♪
♪.. Was his home
And when he died ..♪
♪.. All he left us was alone ..♪
♪.. Papa was a rollin' stone
My son ..♪
(PHONE RINGING)
Don't answer that.
(VOICE SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
..♪..♪..
BOY : Right.
Yeah.
..♪..♪..
(DOORBELL BUZZES)
You Uncle's boy?
- You Jerome?
- Yeah. Come on in.
Come on. Hurry up.
Have a seat.
Make yourself comfortable.
So you bring it?
We good?
Just a sec.
There you go, little man.
What you doing?
You're 500 short.
What are you talking about?
The deal was 25.
- No, the deal was 3.
- No, deal was for 25.
- The deal was 3.
- Wanna call Uncle? Have him tell you?
No, Uncle knows the deal. You call him.
- Hey, you little shit.
- Hey.
You better be easy with that.
I started easy.
Now...
...you owe another 5.
Go in the refrigerator.
There's a stack of cash in there.
There's $1000.
You can take the 5.
..♪..♪..
No, I said you could take 5.
- You lied.
- Oh, okay.
Okay, don't even worry about it,
little man.
♪.. Sittin' here, guess I didn't make bail ..♪
♪.. Got time and a story to tell ..♪
WOMAN : Thank you.
♪.. Started when I was 9 years old ..♪
♪.. Woke up and Daddy was gone ..♪
♪.. I started hustlin'
And they couldn't tell me nothin' ..♪
♪.. Frontin' in the hood
Trying to be somebody ..♪
♪.. My soul was on empty ..♪
♪.. I was searchin' for something ..♪
♪.. Tried to be good ..♪
♪.. Tried to keep from trouble ..♪
♪.. Livin' too fast ..♪
♪.. Tryin' to make good on a hustle ..♪
♪.. Sometimes it gets lonely ..♪
♪.. Comin' from where I'm from
I'm from ..♪
♪.. Sometimes
Ain't what they seem to be ..♪
♪.. Comin' from where I'm from
I'm from ..♪
♪.. Sometimes you get a little angry ..♪
UNCLE : Stop talking.
Stop talking. Shut up.
You're making my head hurt.
You're late. Get in here. Sit down.
Because that is your job.
..♪..♪..
Shut the door.
Shut the door!
What is this?
You have crumbs on your shirt.
I didn't give you cash for food.
That means you take from bag.
Look at me.
You want I cut the tip of your finger off
for stealing? Is that what you want?
Give it to me.
The pastry was 3.
I used 20 and put the rest back.
I got an extra 500 from the mark.
You what?
He tried to short us 5, so I handled it.
Still doesn't mean
you get to steal from me.
Come on, Danny. We feed you here.
You don't go starving.
Your second time.
It's the second time you steal from me.
I was hungry.
Next time you steal from me,
I cut your hand off. I put it in refrigerator.
For that, I send you back out now.
Get up.
..♪..♪..
♪.. 'Cause I'm just a soul
Whose intentions are good ..♪
♪.. Oh, Lord
Please don't let me be misunderstood ..♪
DANNY : Hey!
Hey! Asshole!
Hey.
♪.. Baby, you understand me now ..♪
♪.. Sometimes you see I'm mad ..♪
♪.. No one can always be an angel ..♪
♪.. Sometimes you see some bad ..♪
♪.. Well, I'm just a soul
Whose intentions are good ..♪
♪.. Oh, Lord
Please don't let me be misunderstood ..♪
Back from the dead, huh?
Where am I?
..♪..♪..
You're safe.
You're in my apartment.
And who the hell are you?
I'm Mary.
You were hurt. Passed out in an alley.
Come on. Eat.
- Where's my bag?
- You'll get it back.
- Everything inside it too.
- I need it now.
Sit down.
I need to get back.
Back where?
I'm supposed to go to Back Bay.
I tell you what.
You sit down, have some food...
...I'll take you to Back Bay myself.
How's that?
Whoa, slow down.
When's the last time you ate?
So, what's in Back Bay?
Your mother.
- What, you got family or friends there?
- What's with all the questions, lady?
You a cop?
Not exactly.
I'm just trying to help. That's all.
- Yeah? I don't need your help.
- Hmm.
See, I think you do, especially knowing
what's in that backpack of yours.
Let me guess: two bricks of brown...
...and a semiautomatic handgun?
Hmm?
The man who gave you that bag,
what's his name?
- He'll kill me for talking to you.
- He won't lay a finger on you.
He'll kill us both.
You know what happens...
...if you get busted with that bag?
Hmm?
- The cops will turn you into an informant.
- Yeah?
- Well, I ain't no snitch, so...
- Yeah, well, that doesn't matter.
All that matters is what people think.
And nobody likes talking to kids
who talks to cops. Right?
Especially where we come from.
Look, I'm on your side.
Come on, let's clean up that cut.
You got blood all over your shirt.
Stay right here.
Here you go.
Who did that to you?
Uncle?
- How you know Uncle?
- Don't worry about that.
Did he do that to you?
Where you going?
To teach somebody some manners.
Shit. I'm coming with you.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
..♪..♪..
- What are you about to do?
- You just stay in the car.
Keep the doors locked. Okay?
Put your hood on.
What can I do for you?
It's all there. He didn't touch a thing.
A bit out of the way for you, isn't it?
I thought I'd, uh, return it.
- We don't want hard feelings.
- No hard feelings?
- Yeah.
- Oh.
You think because you're
Benny goddamn Spencer's girl...
...you get to walk in here and shoot
your mouth off like a parrot with tits?
(MEN CHUCKLING)
Okay, all right.
Now you're just being rude.
Danny belongs to me.
Danny belongs to no one.
It's all right. You know, I like your style.
No hard feelings.
Why don't you go get the little thief?
Bring him up here.
And then in a few years...
...if I don't want him anymore...
...and if he's still alive,
maybe I sell him to you.
I think you mean if you're still alive.
..♪..♪..
MAN : Uncle?
What did you do?
I just fucked up.
Bad.
You sleeping on the sofa, okay?
You should be comfortable.
(PHONE BUZZES)
Uh...
I gotta run out for a bit.
- You just gonna leave me in your house?
- Yeah. Why not?
- I could rob you.
- Yeah, but you're not.
Make yourself at home.
Get whatever you want out of the fridge.
You know where the bathroom is.
Takes a minute for hot water to come up.
One rule:
Stay out of my room.
..♪..♪..
(CHATTERING)
(DOOR HANDLE RATTLING)
You can't check in?
Heh. My phone died.
Someone took out Uncle and his crew.
Kozlovs think it was us.
Where's Benny?
- His office.
- I'll be up.
..♪..♪..
The Kozlovs think we did this
to take Uncle's territory.
- That's ridiculous.
- Of course it is.
Whoever killed that douche bag
did the world a favor.
- Who did it?
WALTER : Asshole like him...
- ...everyone's a suspect.
- Okay, Walter.
We gotta make a move
before they retaliate.
- Last thing we want is another war.
- Maybe exactly what we need is a war.
Maybe he's right, Pop.
Mary?
Mary.
You've been so quiet.
Oh...
I was just thinking.
You're right.
We don't need another war.
We need to put this to bed now.
Torn.
- Arrange a meeting for tomorrow.
- You got it, Pop.
You went through my things last night.
I thought I told you
to stay out of my room.
Oh, you think that's funny?
No.
Why you got guns in your room?
You didn't see any guns.
Do you understand me?
I said, do you understand me?
Yeah, I got it.
(SIGHS)
The next time I tell you to do something,
you better listen.
We understand each other?
I got it.
Because I gotta leave, but I'll be back.
Stay in this apartment. Lock the door.
Do not answer it
under any circumstance.
Do you understand me?
Yeah, whatever, man.
Don't "whatever" me.
What are you gonna do, huh?
If you gonna hit me, just do it.
Sorry.
..♪..♪..
Please spare me your sympathy.
Take this. Here.
Uncle was my father's youngest brother.
Not his brightest and not my favorite...
...but he was family.
What we want is justice.
We're here to avoid
any misunderstanding.
Tell me, how do we know it wasn't
the pervert Walter King?
He and Uncle always had bad blood.
Whoever killed Uncle
was not sanctioned by me.
But if they work for me, I can assure you
they will be dealt with immediately.
You've always been a smart man.
But what you asking me to do, Benny?
Forgive and forget?
He's telling you, be careful
where you point your fingers.
Anyone could have done this,
but if it's one of my people...
...you have my word.
I appreciate that.
And now there's something else
I would like to discuss.
- The West End.
- What about it'?
- Give it to us.
- Are you out of your mind?
- In the matter of reparation.
- I didn't come to renegotiate territories.
But I will definitely give
this matter serious consideration.
You do that, Benny.
- I promise you, Luka.
- Good.
(CLAPPING)
Thank you, Benny.
(ENGINE STARTS)
..♪..♪..
So they think they're gonna use
that bullshit as leverage...
...to reallocate territory? No way.
We need to find out who the hell started
this mess by wasting Uncle.
Walter.
Luka said Uncle
and Walter had bad blood.
Uncle called him a perv.
He said Walter abused one of his boys.
We need to find out who started this
and take that son of a bitch out.
No. No, we just need
to throw him a bone.
That's bullshit.
- We need to send the right message.
- Just give him Walter.
- He targeted Uncle before. Luka said so.
- That was a long time ago.
Come on, man, grudges don't die.
You know that.
He hates him. You heard him.
If anybody wanted Uncle dead,
it would be Walter.
She's not wrong.
Walter would be
the only one arrogant enough...
...to make a move without my blessing.
Mary. And you will do this?
TOM : He jogs every day at 3 p.m.
Like clockwork.
- Done.
- So be it.
I'll sell it to Luka.
Hey.
You okay?
- What you mean about Uncle?
- What about him?
You said I ain't have to worry
about him no more.
You don't.
No one does.
Oh, shit.
- Badass.
- Hey.
- What the hell are you? Some kind of...?
- Your mouth.
Look, I told you I wasn't gonna let
anybody touch you, and I meant it.
So you do all that for me, huh?
Damn sure didn't do it for myself.
Well, thanks.
That's dope.
But you know he got friends.
They could be looking for me right now.
Here.
- So, lady...
- Mary.
Please. Thank you.
Fine. Mary.
Why do you got all them guns
in your room?
The ones I didn't see.
- Business.
- What kind of business?
Security, okay?
- "Security" like protection?
- Yep.
Protection for who?
- None of your business.
- Why you got that cash in your room?
Okay, look, not your business again.
Do you like hot dogs, fat mouth?
- No shit. Who don't like hot dogs?
- Watch your...
- I'm hungry as a mother...
- Uh-uh.
I got a lot of work to do with you.
I'm playing with you,
you know that, right'?
You need to be careful with how you play
with adults because I don't play.
- Is that right?
- Yeah, that's right.
Better be glad you like hot dogs.
I don't trust people
who don't like a good dog.
How you like yours?
I don't know. Ketchup?
Ketchup? That's all?
- I'd like mine with the works, please.
- What's "the works"?
Everything-
- Two with the works.
- Two?
What you gonna eat?
You better make that four.
Yeah, I could eat these all day long.
I don't even want to know what's in them.
How about we, um, sit on that bench
over there...
...and knock these puppies out?
Mm... I got a better idea.
..♪..♪..
This is where I come to escape.
Pretty cool, huh?
Beyond cool.
Yeah.
Before she left us...
...my mom used to take me here.
Used to sit out on the water.
Big sack lunches.
Feed the seagulls.
My father was killed.
A year ago.
After that, I went to go stay
with my grandma till she died.
And then what?
They wanted to send me
to some home for boys.
Who?
Those assholes at Child Services.
I ran.
Lived in the parks for some time.
Then one of Uncle's boys found me.
I guess you know the rest.
(SNIFFS)
Finish your hot dog.
..♪..♪..
Hey. Listen up.
I gotta talk to you for a second. Look.
Listen, as long as you're here,
you keep that door locked...
...and don't you open it.
Don't go anywhere.
You being here is our secret, right?
- Yeah, yeah.
- No, no, no, look at me.
No "yeah, yeah." This is serious. Okay?
I got it.
"I got it." Let me see that ball.
Stop bouncing it on my wall.
(LAUGHING)
I'll be back.
What did I say?
You want me to come back over there?
..♪..♪..
(SILENCED GUNSHOTS)
(SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
TOM : Cover him. Cover!
TOM :
They got five of our best guys.
They put a bullet in Mateo's shoulder.
Derek's in intensive care.
It could've been you or me, Pop.
There's only one thing these animals
understand, and that's an eye for an eye.
I say we hit the Kozlovs back hard now.
Slow...
...down.
We're not starting a war...
...until we're absolutely sure it was them.
You wouldn't have said that
20 years ago.
- What are you trying to say'?
- I'm not trying to say anything.
If you can't handle it, I will.
Omar, what are you thinking?
- Kozlovs.
- Me too. I need proof.
I got it, boss.
..♪..♪..
(DOORBELL BUZZING)
...Your badge? He has a gun. Shoot him!
(BUZZING CONTINUES)
(DOOR CLOSES)
Who the hell are you?
I'm Danny.
Who are you?
- What are you doing here?
Looking for Mary.
She's not answering her phone.
You live around here?
Yeah. Jamaica Plain.
So how you know Mary?
Let's try this again.
How you know Mary?
From around.
- How you know Mary?
- We work together.
In security business?
Security business.
That's a good one. As soon as
she gets home, you tell her to call me.
It's very important.
You understand that?
Okay.
Give her the message.
..♪..♪..
Danny?
I told you not to go...
- ...in my goddamn room.
- You lied to me.
- I lied to you?
- Yeah.
What, you think I'm stupid?
I told you not to go through my things,
Danny.
Your friend came over. Nice guy.
Tom? And you let him in?
He had a key.
(CHUCKLES)
- Is that your boyfriend?
- Not anymore.
Yeah, but he was.
- Look, it's complicated, kid.
- Complicated how?
Let's just say,
Tom is now like a brother to me.
- But he wasn't always.
- No, Oprah, he wasn't.
- What the hell was he doing in here?
- I don't know.
Well, what did he say'?
He said you're not in security.
That's for damn sure.
- Yeah, well, Tom is an asshole.
- Duh.
- What else did he say?
- He said he wanted you to call him.
It was important. It was urgent.
He was pretty pissed.
Lady...
...what is it that you really do?
I'm a nun. I'm a goddamn nun.
What's it to you, you nosy little shit?
Okay, you know what?
You want me to leave? I'll go!
Okay, fine. There's the door. Go.
- Is that what you want?
- Did I say that's what I want? Did I?
..♪..♪..
Look...
...you don't have to worry
about Tom, okay?
This is about you and me.
This is about us.
You understand?
Yeah.
Good.
..♪..♪..
You kept your key?
Why can't I reach you no more?
Called you, no answer.
Texted you, no answer.
Radio silence. Not a call.
What's so goddamn important
you had to barge into...?
Kozlovs tried to hit Pop.
That's what's important.
- After we gave them Walter?
- They hit him before.
They don't care about Walter.
They're trying to use it
as an opportunity to take out Benny.
How do you know?
Come on.
(SCREAMING)
Look at me.
No.
(SCREAMING)
TOM : I'm not asking you again.
BENNY : Do you know how long
he's been in there with Tom?
Two hours.
You know what he's told him?
- Everything.
- What's our next move?
Tom's new friend volunteered
that Luka will be hosting a meeting...
...for all the members
of the family this Friday.
I need you and Tom
to deliver a message.
I understand.
I hear you've taken in a stray.
Yeah, it's no big deal.
I was gonna tell you.
And yet, you didn't.
So you're mad at me?
Should I be?
He was hurt. He needed help.
He's only been with me a couple days.
- How old?
- Twelve.
Or 13. I don't really know.
So bring him over
to the house for dinner.
It's Mina's birthday.
What's up?
We was just talking about
your mother's birthday party.
With everything, we're having a party?
You want to tell her that
her 65th birthday party's been canceled?
- TOM : No.
- Okay.
Hey.
Let's get this done.
Why do I need a sport coat?
I can't even pronounce half of this stuff.
Because you've been
invited somewhere.
- So?
- And a proper young man...
...wears a proper jacket.
Besides, we need to get you
a new sweatshirt.
- What's wrong with my hoodie?
- When is the last time you washed it'?
- "Washed"?
- Exactly. Come here.
Give it here.
Thank you very much.
- Here.
- We'll get a new... Watch the attitude.
- And you gonna get some new jeans too.
- I like that hoodie.
This is nice. Look at this.
- Blue hoodie.
- It's all right.
No?
- I think this one suits you perfectly.
MARY : Oh, that is nice.
- I hate it.
MARY : Uh, excuse me.
- What the hell is that?
- Come here.
It's called respect, all right?
Put the damn jacket on.
- I don't wanna put the damn jacket...
- Watch your mouth.
- You look very handsome.
- Yes.
- I look like a douche bag.
- Ah.
Language.
Perhaps he'd be more comfortable at...
- No, we're good right here.
- Oh, well...
So who's gonna be at this thing
you keep telling me about?
Family.
Well, if it's family,
isn't a nice shirt good enough?
No, it's not.
- Not for Benny.
- Who's Benny?
- Tom's father.
- Oh.
- You mean Tom, your boyfriend?
- Oh, shut up. He's not my boyfriend.
- Mm-hm.
- Anyway, Benny's Tom's father...
...and he used to take care of me
when I was a kid.
Take care of you
like you take care of me?
Kind of.
Kind of how?
(SIGHS)
When I was a kid, my father,
he wasn't nice to me and my mom.
So when I got old enough to run,
I ran away.
And I was living in the streets for a while.
Like me?
Yep, just like you.
Here she come again.
- How's this?
- Much better.
Try it on. Here.
- Try it on.
- I don't wanna try it on.
- Come on, now. Move.
- I want out of this bougie-ass neighbor...
Watch your mouth.
It's classy.
Yes, look at you. See, you like it.
Change is good. Come on.
MARY : Remember what I told you
about Benny, right?
If he starts asking questions?
Don't tell him who I worked for,
and don't tell him about Uncle.
That's right.
Damn.
MARY : Come here.
What's your last name?
- Warren.
- Danny Warren from...?
- Dorchester.
- Mm-hm. What street?
- Norfolk Avenue.
- Mm-hm.
What about your parents?
I never met them.
I was in a lot of foster homes,
but they didn't work out.
That's right.
Look...
...I don't care how nice Benny is to you.
He is not to be trusted.
He is not your friend.
Remember that.
Okay.
Now, let's go over this again.
What's your last name?
- Danny Warren.
BENNY : Danny Warren, huh?
- Where you from?
- Dorchester.
One of my best friends growing up
was named Danny.
We called him "Danny Boy." Heh.
Anybody ever call you that?
Some people.
BENNY : I wanna toast my wife.
To 45 more years of happiness.
- Happy birthday, Mina.
- Happy birthday, beautiful.
Thank you. Thank you.
(OVER STEREO) ♪.. I do love you ..♪
Whoo.
- What do I hear? Shoot. Ha-ha.
MINA : Oh, Jesus. Oh, my God.
BENNY : You remember
how we used to dance to this?
MARY : Uh-oh.
- Benny move.
- Like Fred and Ginger.
- Oh, no. Ginger's tired tonight, baby.
- Oh, no.
Well, Mary, it's me and you.
(BENNY HUMMING)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
- Good luck, girl.
- Yes. I'm gonna need it.
♪.. Ooh, yes, I do, girl ..♪
You've seemed distracted.
What's on your mind?
Well, just...
Just something I've been thinking about
the last couple of days.
- What?
- Well, I...
I'm just thinking that it's time for me
to move on, you know?
I just wanna do something else
with my life.
Look at me, sweetheart.
Is this about Tom?
No, it's not about him.
It's about me.
Oh, okay, then.
Well, this can wait till tomorrow.
Because today is about Mina.
- Of course. Mm-hm.
- All right?
Okay.
MINA : I could never understand how
people could just give up their children.
I better get back out there to him.
MINA : Hi, baby.
- Mm. Red velvet.
MINA : It's good.
- Happy birthday, Mom.
- Thank you.
TOM : Yes, please.
Would you mind taking Danny a slice,
Mama? Give me a sec with Mary?
MINA : Sure.
TOM : All right, thanks.
Thank you.
You look real beautiful tonight.
So, what's on your mind, Tom?
- The kid.
- What about him?
- Cleans up real nice.
- Mm-hm.
- Danny Warren from Dorchester.
- Yep.
He told me Jamaica Plain.
So I asked myself:
"Why would a kid from Jamaica Plain
say he's from Dorchester?"
What's your point?
Then I seemed to remember,
wasn't there a hit...
...on a bookie last year
from Jamaica Plain?
- What was the last name?
- I don't remember.
Miller.
Funny. I also remember a news story
that mentioned a kid that survived.
- Don't make this about us.
- You said there was no kid.
Yeah, because I don't do kids,
and you know that.
- That's not the point.
- It was for me.
- Did he see you?
- No.
- Did you see him?
Mary, is there any way that kid
can connect this family to that hit?
- No.
- You better hope not.
- Where'd you find him?
- I'm not doing this tonight.
And I'm not doing it here.
Just leave the kid out of this.
How you think the old man's gonna react
when he hears this?
Maybe we should go over there
and tell him together.
I mean, you know how he loves secrets.
We don't need no more problems.
This thing with the kid...
...it could turn out
to be very dangerous, Mary.
- People find out who...
- That's not gonna happen.
- What if the old man doesn't like it?
- What if I go tell your father...
...you called him "the old man"?
- Oh, Tom, what are you doing?
- I'm trying to apologize.
- I'm sorry.
- Mm-hm.
I'm not gonna say nothing about the kid...
...or his name to the old man.
I just want us back the way we were.
Tom, I can't do this with you, okay?
Come here, come here, come here.
Tell me you didn't love me.
For so many years.
And that girl never stopped loving you.
- I'm just not that girl anymore.
- What's that even mean?
It means
I should probably get Danny home.
You need to get some rest.
We have a big job tomorrow.
MARY : Good morning.
You hungry?
Cereal.
He said I could come over
whenever I want.
- Huh?
- Benny.
What about him?
He said I could come over
whenever I want.
Danny, look, I, uh...
You know that money you found
in my closet? With the guns?
If something happens...
...I want you to have it, okay?
It's yours.
Okay. What are you talking about?
I just... I just want you
to be prepared, okay?
You know where we from. If you stay
ready, you ain't gotta get ready, right?
That money is your freedom.
Okay?
..♪..♪..
I want you to take that money,
and I want you to run.
I want you to run as fast as you can.
I want you to buy you a real nice life.
Okay?
Promise me that.
Promise me.
I promise.
Okay.
Go ahead and eat.
..♪..♪..
- Why didn't you tell me?
- What?
Pop says you're talking
about getting out again.
- Is it because of me?
- No, it's not because of you.
So why didn't you tell me?
You're just gonna retire?
And then what?
Open up a bed-and-breakfast
with the kid?
This is not a life
you just choose to leave.
Mary, you know that.
The old man's not gonna let you
just walk out of here.
Besides, you know too much.
You'd be a liability.
He's telling you what you wanna hear.
Always has.
What is it you're pretending
not to understand?
Wake up.
No one leaves.
(EXHALES)
..♪..♪..
(SPEAKING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
(SILENCED GUNSHOTS)
(SILENCED GUNSHOT)
(SPEAKING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
(CHATTERING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
(SILENCED GUNSHOT)
(BODY THUDS)
(GRUNTING)
(YELLS)
(SPEAKING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
(GROANS)
(FRANTIC CHATTER
IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
Where's Luka?
Wrong answer.
(GROANS)
MARY : I'm okay.
- Slow down, Mary.
(MARY GROANS)
Would you just slow down?
- Goddamn it.
- Stop.
I'm not your responsibility no more, okay?
We got them, Pop. Message delivered.
- Where's Mary?
- She took a hit, but...
- She took a hit?
- Yeah. She's fine.
Well, where the hell is she?
- She didn't want help.
- She didn't want your help.
- Wasn't for me, she'd be dead right now.
- If it wasn't for you, she'd be here.
- I'm not losing her.
- Think I want her to leave?
- I don't know what you want.
- Well, I don't.
Which is why you gotta know
about the kid.
What about the kid?
(GROANS)
DANNY : What's going on?
- Nothing.
Just a scrape.
It's fine, honey.
It's just a scratch, okay?
- You okay?
- Go back to bed. It's okay.
Go back to bed.
I just need to lay down
for a minute, okay?
(MARY PANTING)
Mary. What you need?
Can I get you something?
Oh, uhn... I just need to lay down
and close my eyes...
...for a couple of minutes, baby.
That's all.
(SIGHS)
When you're better, we'll go, right?
We'll get out of here?
Go somewhere far away, like you said?
(LAUGHING)
Tom was right.
He ain't never gonna let me go.
- I tried.
- Well, try again. That's bullshit, Mary.
(GROANS)
I tried.
..♪..♪..
(SNIFFS)
♪.. Ain't no love
In the heart of the city ..♪
In the heart of town ..♪
♪.. Ain't no love
And it's sure enough a pity ..♪
'Cause you ain't around ..♪
Danny?
♪.. Ain't no love
In the heart of the city ..♪
In the heart of town ..♪
Danny?
♪.. Ain't no love
And it's sure enough a pity ..♪
'Cause you ain't around ..♪
♪.. Whoa ..♪
♪.. Whoa H'
(SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
I'm here to see Benny.
Here to see Benny?
Who the hell are you?
Danny.
- Friend of Mary's.
MAN : All right. Hold on, man.
Yeah.
I got this kid here to see Benny.
Said he's a friend of Mary's.
Name's Danny.
- Yeah.
- Tell him it's Danny Boy.
Danny Boy.
Yeah. No, he's alone.
All right.
Go ahead.
Danny Boy.
Where's Mary?
I came alone.
How is she? Tom says she was hurt.
She's gonna be fine.
That's good.
Something on your mind?
Danny?
You gotta let her go.
Hmm.
And I know Tom said
you're never gonna, but...
...you gotta.
Danny, these are family matters.
It's better you avoid getting mixed up
in something...
- ...you don't understand.
- I understand fine.
Okay?
I mean, I'm not, like...
...stupid or nothing.
Well, now that I know
you're not stupid or nothing...
...this is what you're gonna do.
You're gonna run back home
and tell Mary...
...that I would like to see her.
And that if she's hurt...
...we'll arrange for her
to receive proper medical treatment.
I don't think so.
Oh, you don't?
No.
I don't.
Huh.
She doesn't work for you anymore.
You're a brave boy.
I see that.
But you're making a mistake.
I'm gonna tell you a story, Danny.
Let's see.
I guess it was about a year ago.
I sent Mary on a contract
in Jamaica Plain.
This particular mark was a bookie...
...who was in debt for over $100,000.
..♪..♪..
Marcus Miller.
- You're lying.
- Mary didn't find you, Danny Miller.
She was following you.
- You're lying.
- Really?
None of this sounds familiar?
I thought so.
You're upset. It's understandable.
But put the gun down.
Now, you can put it down on the floor...
...or I can come and take it from you.
It's okay. I understand.
I love Mary too. We all love Mary.
But she's not who you think she is.
She's only looking after you...
...because she feels guilty.
And why shouldn't she?
She made you an orphan.
(SNIFFLES)
Hey.
- Everything is gonna...
MARY : Let him go.
Go get in the car.
Go.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Tom says you were hurt.
- You don't look well.
- Put the gun down.
Danny and I are getting out of here.
So I see.
Yeah, my debt to you is paid.
Your debt?
I took care of you. Gave you a family.
- Was like a father to you.
- Is that what you tell yourself?
I taught you to survive.
Yeah, well, it's time for me
to move on now.
(SIGHS)
Mary, heh, baby.
You're acting crazy. Stop it.
You know how much I love you.
Well, if you love me...
...Benny, let me go.
Please let me go.
No.
You ungrateful bitch.
Debt?
You don't owe me a debt.
I own you.
And you're not going anywhere.
You're gonna stay in the family
and work for me.
And you will train Danny
to work for the family...
...just like I trained you.
If you leave...
...we will find you and the boy.
So you see?
You're not going anywhere.
Now...
...look at me...
...and tell me that you understand.
Mary...
...I need you to look at me...
...and tell me you understand.
I understand.
(CRIES SOFTLY)
(MEN GRUNT)
(TIRES SQUEALING)
Of course.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
..♪..♪..
- Where is he?
MAN : Upstairs in his office.
- Cops know yet?
- No, not yet.
Shut this place down. No calls in or out.
- Nobody talks to nobody.
- You got it, Tom.
..♪..♪..
- Give me a second.
MAN : Everybody out.
- Tom.
- Not now.
Sorry, boss, but I think
you're gonna wanna hear this.
Jerome.
Get in here.
Tell him what you saw.
- A kid.
- What kid?
JEROME : One of Uncle's boys.
I was outside,
unloading the last of the containers...
...and I seen this kid come
into the warehouse.
He talked to Rick and Maurice.
Maurice made a call
and let him come upstairs.
And?
About 10 minutes later,
all of a sudden I see this kid...
...come running down
like the place was on fire.
You sure?
Yeah.
Pulled a gun on me once.
And he was alone?
Yeah, as far as I could tell.
Yeah, okay.
Hey.
So it's true what Benny said?
About my father.
Danny...
...there's not a moment...
...of my life that I don't regret that hit
on your father.
Mom left that son of a bitch
when I was 7.
The only thing
she forgot to take was me.
She forgot to take me.
But he said you're only
taking care of me out of guilt.
No, that's not true.
All right, maybe it was at first.
But it's not now.
You lied to me.
I mean, you don't care about me.
- I do.
- No, you don't.
Danny, I do. I care about you, okay?
That's why I found you.
How?
How'd you find me?
A photo from your house...
...from that day.
I saw you too.
(SNIFFLING)
So I asked around...
...and eventually, I found out
you were one of Uncle's boys.
So I started watching you.
I didn't know
how I was gonna approach you, so...
...that day, when I saw you in the...
In the alley, hurt...
I can understand if you hate me, Danny.
I can understand if you want me dead.
But they're gonna come after you.
(PHONE BUZZING)
They're gonna come after you.
You gotta let me fix this, okay?
We gotta go. Come on.
..♪..♪..
All right. Stay in the car.
If you see anyone,
hit the horn three times.
- Got it?
- I got it.
Be back.
(PHONE BUZZING)
(CAR ALARM BLARING)
Shit!
- Where you going?
- Hey! Get your hands off me.
- Calm. Calm down.
- Mary!
(PHONE BUZZES)
MAN : I got the kid.
Says she's expecting us.
I'm sure she is.
Bring him here. We got what she wants.
Let her come get him.
What I'm having a hard time believing...
...is you walked in here...
...and killed him alone.
..♪..♪..
Look at me!
I didn't kill your old man.
- You asshole.
- TOM : Yeah.
I was afraid of that.
Take him upstairs.
Make sure he stays there.
MAN : Let's go, kid.
DANNY : She's still coming for me.
MAN : Come on.
- She's still coming for me.
MAN : Move. Shut up.
(PHONE BUZZES)
Damn.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
..♪..♪..
Tom, that bitch is acting
like she done lost her goddamn mind.
I want every man we got
at every entrance to this place.
♪.. I left a good job in the city ..♪
Let's go! Let's go!
♪.. And I never lost
One minute of sleepin' ..♪
♪.. Worryin' 'bout the way
Things might have been ..♪
- ♪.. Big wheel, keep on turnin' ..♪
- ♪.. Turnin' ..♪
- ♪.. Proud Mary, keep on burnin' ..♪
- ♪.. Burnin' ..♪
♪.. Rollin', rollin'
Rollin' on the river ..♪
♪.. Said we rollin', rollin'
♪.. All right ..♪
♪.. Oh, I cleaned
A lot of plates in Memphis ..♪
♪.. And I pumped a lot of 'tane
Down in New Orleans ..♪
♪.. But I never saw
The good side of the city ..♪
♪.. Till I hitched a ride
On a riverboat queen ..♪
- ♪.. Big wheel, keep on turnin' ..♪
- ♪.. Turnin' ..♪
- ♪.. Proud Mary, keep on burnin' ..♪
- ♪.. Burnin' ..♪
♪.. Rollin', rollin'
Rollin' on the river ..♪
♪.. I tell you, we rollin', rollin'
♪.. All right
Yeah ..♪
(GUNSHOTS)
♪.. If you come down to the river ..♪
♪.. I bet you gonna find
Some people who live ..♪
♪.. And you don't have to worry
If you got no money ..♪
♪.. People on the river
Are happy to give ..♪
- ♪.. Big wheel, keep on turnin' ..♪
- ♪.. Turnin' ..♪
- ♪.. Proud Mary, keep on burnin' ..♪
- ♪.. Burnin' ..♪
♪.. And we rollin', said we rollin'
And we rollin' on the river ..♪
- ♪.. Tell me one more time ..♪
- ♪.. Rollin' ..♪
- ♪.. Yeah, all right ..♪
- ♪.. Rollin' on the river ..♪
- ♪.. Ooh, yeah ..♪
♪.. Yeah, all right ..♪
♪.. Yeah ..♪
(BOTH GRUNTING)
♪.. Oh, I cleaned
A lot of plates in Memphis ..♪
♪.. And I pumped a lot of 'tane
Down in New Orleans ..♪
♪.. But I never saw
The good side of the city ..♪
♪.. Till I hitched a ride
On a riverboat queen ..♪
- ♪.. Big wheel, keep on turnin' ..♪
- ♪.. Turnin' ..♪
- ♪.. Proud Mary, keep on burnin' ..♪
- ♪.. Burnin' ..♪
♪.. And we rollin', we rollin'
We rollin' on the river ..♪
♪.. I tell you, we rollin', rollin'
Rollin' on the river ..♪
(GRUNTS)
♪.. All right, yeah ..♪
- ♪.. Rollin' ..♪
- ♪.. Yeah ..♪
- ♪.. Rollin' on the river ..♪
- ♪.. All right, now ..♪
♪.. Rollin', rollin'
Rollin' on the river ..♪
(GUNSHOTS)
♪.. Yeah, all right I ..♪
(PANTING)
TOM : Mary.
You really fucked up.
(MUFFLED GASP)
..♪..♪..
(MOUTHING) Where is he?
You okay?
TOM : You killed Uncle.
I asked myself, "Why would you
do something so stupid?"
Tom, I'm leaving out of here,
and I'm taking the kid.
TOM : I can't let that happen.
MARY : Come on, Tom.
He didn't do anything.
Let him go.
We can settle this without hurting the kid.
Danny.
I want you to get up
and run out of here...
- Not without you.
- Don't do it, kid. Stay where you are.
I said, get up and go.
- Go!
- Sit down!
- I'll do it. I swear, I will.
- No, you won't, Tom.
You and I both know you can't.
Listen to me.
I need you to hear me.
I'm only gonna say this once.
I'm walking out of here,
I'm gonna find Danny...
...and I'm leaving.
I'm never coming back.
So if you wanna stop me,
you gonna have to kill me.
If it weren't for this family...
...your family, Mary...
...the old man taking you
off the streets...
...you'd be a guttersnipe
servicing cabbies for smack.
News flash,
MARY : you ain't
the mothering type.
You're pathetic.
Don't turn your back on me.
Do not walk away from me.
I will drop you, Mary!
..♪..♪..
News flash, asshole:
I am the mothering type.
..♪..♪..
Danny?
Danny!
Danny...
(CRYING)
..♪..♪..
- What the hell happened to the door?
- I did that saving your ass.
- Well, you took your damn sweet time.
- Hey, your mouth.
♪.. Workin' for the man
Every night and day ..♪
So where we going?
Anywhere you want to, kid.
How about someplace warm and nice?
Now, I like that.
Let's do it. Heh.
Buckle up.
You buckle up.
- You ain't even got a damn door.
- Hey, your mouth.
I'm gonna buckle up your lips.
Let's get out of here.
♪.. And we're rollin' ..♪
♪.. Rollin', yeah ..♪
♪.. Rollin' on the river ..♪
♪.. The river ..♪
♪.. I left a good job in the city ..♪
♪.. Workin' for the man
Every night and day ..♪
♪.. And I never lost
One minute of sleepin' ..♪
♪.. Worryin' 'bout the way
Things might have been ..♪
- ♪.. Big wheel, keep on turnin' ..♪
- ♪.. Turnin' ..♪
- ♪.. Proud Mary, keep on burnin' ..♪
- ♪.. Burnin' ..♪
♪.. Rollin', rollin'
Rollin' on the river ..♪
♪.. Said we rollin', rollin'
♪.. All right ..♪
♪.. Oh, I cleaned
A lot of plates in Memphis ..♪
♪.. And I pumped a lot of 'tane
Down in New Orleans ..♪
♪.. But I never saw
The good side of the city ..♪
♪.. Till I hitched a ride
On a riverboat queen ..♪
- ♪.. Big wheel, keep on turnin' ..♪
- ♪.. Turnin' ..♪
- ♪.. Proud Mary, keep on burnin' ..♪
- ♪.. Burnin' ..♪
♪.. And we rollin', said we rollin'
We rollin' on the river ..♪
♪.. I tell you we rollin', rollin'
Rollin' on the river ..♪
♪.. All right, yeah ..♪
♪.. Ooh, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah ..♪
♪.. If you come down to the river ..♪
♪.. I bet you gonna find
Some people who live ..♪
♪.. And you don't have to worry
If you got no money ..♪
♪.. People on the river
Are happy to give ..♪
- ♪.. Big wheel, keep on turnin' ..♪
- ♪.. Turnin' ..♪
- ♪.. Proud Mary, keep on burnin' ..♪
- ♪.. Burnin' ..♪
♪.. And we rollin', said we rollin'
We rollin' on the river ..♪
- ♪.. Tell me one more time ..♪
- ♪.. Rollin' ..♪
- ♪.. Yeah, all right ..♪
- ♪.. Rollin' on the river ..♪
- ♪.. Ooh, yeah ..♪
Subtitles by FrancisSubs
^.^.^.^.COLORED by.^.^.^.^
® Sud_Arun collections ®
A member of Psagmeno.com
♪.. Yeah, yeah ..♪
♪.. All right, uh-huh ..♪
..♪..♪..